Up at the top, we have all of the set-up code,
في الأعلى لدينا جميع الأكواد التي تم إعدادها،
and here's where we kick off the first fetch request.
وهنا حيث نقوم بإجراء أول طلب إحضار.
We make a request to unsplash's API for an image search,
نقدّم طلب واجهة برمجة تطبيقات إلى موقع إلى unsplash للبحث عن صورة،
and we pass along the required headers,
ثم نقوم بتمرير الرؤوس المطلوبة،
convert the response to JSON,
نُحول الاستجابة إلى JSON،
and then pass the actual JSON data off to the addImage function.
ثم نمرر بيانات JSON الحقيقية إلى دالة addImage.
If there's a problem with the request,
في حال وجود أي مشكلة مع الطلب،
then this line will receive the error and call
سيستقبل هذا السطر الخطأ ويستدعي
the requestError function with the error and that it was the image request that failed.
دالة requestError مصحوبة بالخطأ وهذا كان طلب الصورة الفاشل.
This makes a request for the New York Times articles and
إن هذا يقوم بإنشاء طلب لمقالات صحيفة نيويورك تايمز
it's very similar to the fetch request for unsplash.
ويُشبه كثيرًا طلب الإحضار لـ unsplash.
It sends the request to the New York Times API and it converts
يُرسل الطلب إلى API  صحيفة نيويورك تايمز ويحول الاستجابة إلى
the response to JSON and passes the JSON data to the addArticles function.
JSON ويمرر بيانات JSON إلى دالة addArticles.
If there's a problem with this fetch request,
في حال وجود أي مشكلة مع طلب الإحضار هذا،
the catch method will also call the requestError function,
سيستدعي أسلوب catch دالة requestError،
passing it the error and that it was the articles requests that failed.
مصحوبة بالخطأ وهذه كانت طلبات المقالات الفاشلة.
We looked at the addImage function earlier,
ألقينا نظرة على دالة addImage مُسبقًا،
so let's get down to the addArticles function.
لذا دعونا ننتقل لدالة addArticles في الأسفل.
This code will loop over all of the articles,
سيُكوّن هذا الكود حلقة حول جميع المقالات،
adding them to an unordered list.
يضيفهم إلى القائمة غير المرتبة.
If there aren't any articles,
إذا لم يكن هناك أي مقالات،
then it displays this error message.
فسيظهر لكم رسالة الخطأ هذه.
And that's basically all there is to our app.
ويُعد هذا كل أساسيات تطبيقنا.